A Guide to the Richmond (Va.), Bureau of Permits and Inspections, Building permit architectural blueprints and specifications, 1907-1976
Library of Virginia
- Blueprint drawings, 1907-1950, 3167 sets of blueprints
  - Store Buildings, 1908-1948
    - Store - Permit Number: 12989A, Alterations and Additions to Buildings at 107-09-11 South 7th Street, Address: 107-09-11 South 7th St., 1924 (Folder 915)
      Drawn by: Henry T. Barnham; Contractor: E. L. Bass; Commissioned by: Times-Dispatch Publishing Co., Inc.; Notes: Alterations and additions of office space in existing brick building complex.
    - Store - Permit Number: 13164, Store Building, Address: 24-26 Brookland Boulevard, 1924 (Folder 1044)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Robert L. Wallerstein; Commissioned by: Robert L. Wallerstein; Notes: Two-story, brick store building.
    - Store - Permit Number: 13[sic], Store Building for Mr. Frederick (Fritz) Sitterding, Address: 8 South 12th St., 1924 (Folder 1058)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: W. L. Ragland; Commissioned by: Frederick Sitterding; Notes: 2- story brick store building with street level store front delineated by plate glass.
    - Store - Permit Number: 12749, Store and Flat for L. L. Strause and C.L. Gunst, Address: 2001 Rosewood Ave., 1924 (Folder 1036)
      Drawn by: Max Ruehrmund; Contractor: Max Ruehrmund; Commissioned by: L. L. Strause and C. L. Gunst; Notes: Two-story brick townhouse building designed as a first floor store and second floor flat.
    - Store - Permit Number: 13776A, Plan for Remodeling Store, Address: 215 W. Broad St., 1925 (Folder 1377)
      Drawn by: Bascom J. Rowlett, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: Owner; Commissioned by: W. H. & G. M. Schwartzshield; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 16031, Store for O. H. Berry Co., Address: 511 - 513 E. Grace St., 1925 (Folder 1512)
      Drawn by: Baskervill & Lambert, Architects, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: Graham Construction Co.; Commissioned by: O. H. Berry & Co.; Notes: CD # 112-116, and 116A-B.
    - Store - Permit Number: 14825, Alterations and Additions to Store for Mr. J. F. B. Jurgens, 421 E. Broad St., Address: 421 E. Broad St., 1925 (Folder 1517)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: J. T. Wilson; Commissioned by: F. H. Jurgens; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 14144A, Alterations to Portion of Present Coliseum, West Broad Street, Address: 1337 - 1345 W. Broad St., 1925 (Folder 1376)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., Architects & Builders, Richmond, Va., L. Otis Spiers, Architect; Contractor: Davis Bros.; Commissioned by: Advance Realty Co.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 14422, Store & Flat for Mr. R. E. L. Glasgow, Address: 1710 W. Main St., 1925 (Folder 1159)
      Drawn by: W. B. Newel, Architect; Contractor: E. C. Wilkinson; Commissioned by: R. E. L. Glasgow; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 15453, Richmond Auto Exchange, Address: 1807 W. Marshall St., 1925 (Folder 1372)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: J. E. Crass; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 14364A, Alterations to 427 East Broad St., Address: 427 E. Broad St., 1925 (Folder 1198)
      Drawn by: Construction Dept., McCrory Stores Corp., 1107 Broadway, N.Y.C.; Contractor: J. T. Wilson Inc.; Commissioned by: Mc Cory, Inc.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 13832A, Buildings for Gallaher, Ltd., N. E. Cor. 22nd & Franklin St., City, Address: 23 N. 22nd St., 1925 (Folder 1390)
      Drawn by: L. P. Hartsook, Architect, American Nat'l. Bank Building, Richmond; Contractor: E. L. Bass; Commissioned by: Gallaher, Ltd.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 14591A, Alterations and Additions to Store, Kaynco Realty Corp., Address: 403-5 E. Broad St., 1925 (Folder 924)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Challenge Co.; Commissioned by: Kaynco Realty Corp.; Notes: See Control #923. Kaufmann Stores Building
    - Store - Permit Number: 15266, Store for Mr. E. W. Newman, Address: 412 E. Grace St., 1925 (Folder 1396)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: J. T. Wilson; Commissioned by: E. W. Newman; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 15652, Three Story Store, Address: 16 E. Broad St., 1925 (Folder 1379)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: J. T. Nuckols; Commissioned by: Warner Moore, Jr.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 14594, Store Building for C. W. Vaughn Hardware Co., Address: 315 N. First St.., 1925 (Folder 1458)
      Drawn by: Henry T. Barnham, Architect and Engineer, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Allen Saville Inc.; Commissioned by: C. W. Vaughn Hardware Co.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 15172, Store Building for Mr. Otto Gregnanni, Address: 314 N. 2nd St., 1925 (Folder 1403)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros. Inc.; Contractor: E. L. Bass; Commissioned by: Otto Gregnanni; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 14550, Warehouse for Southern Electric Co., Address: 401 E. Canal St., 1925 (Folder 1451)
      Drawn by: Marcellus E. Wright, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: R. M. Anderson Inc.; Commissioned by: Southern Electric Co.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 14656, Alterations and Additions to Store for the Fauntleroy Estate, 417 E. Broad St., Address: 417 E. Broad St., 1925 (Folder 1454)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: John T. Wilson Co.; Commissioned by: Fauntleroy Estate (Alice L. Breeden); Notes: Signage in the window of the elevation of the building indicates it was for the Richmond store, Hofheimer's.
    - Store - Permit Number: 14320A, Additions and Alterations to Store Building, Address: 419 E. Broad St., 1925 (Folder 1505)
      Drawn by: Construction Dept., McCrory Stores Corp., 1107 Broadway, N.Y.C.; Contractor: J. T. Wilson; Commissioned by: McCrory Stores Corp.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 15383, Store and Flat for Mr. Harry Levy, Address: 420 Louisiana St., 1925 (Folder 1416)
      Drawn by: I. T. Skinner, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Owner; Commissioned by: Harry Levy; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 14425A, Alterations to Building at 633 East Broad St., SW Cor. Seventh St. for Lewis K. Leggitt Co., Address: 633 E. Broad St., 1925 (Folder 1193)
      Drawn by: Walter Thomas Williams, Architect, --- East 42nd Street, New York City; Contractor: Doyle and Russell; Commissioned by: Lewis K. Leggitt Co.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 15669, Brick Undertaking Establishment, Address: 104 N. Belvedere St., 1925 (Folder 1688)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., Inc., Designers & Builders, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: Davis Bros.; Commissioned by: A. W. Bennett; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 17125, Drug Store and Flat Building for Geo. W. Johnson, Address: 2536 Lombardy, 1926 (Folder 555)
      Drawn by: A. W. Harmon, Inc., Builders and Engineers, 15 N. 11th St., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: A. W. Harmon, Inc.; Commissioned by: George W. Johnson; Notes: Two-story brick and stucco commercial building. The first floor is a drugstore space, and the second floor plan is a 2-bedroom apartment with one bath, living room and dining room.
    - Store - Permit Number: 16626, Store Building for John T. Wilson, Address: 212 - 214 N. 4th St., 1926 (Folder 1272)
    - Store - Permit Number: 16078, Drawings for Store Building No. 207 E. Franklin St. and Alterations to the Adjacent Store Building No. 209 E. Franklin for Mr. R. G. Cabell, Address: 297 E. Franklin St., 1926 (Folder 1556)
      Drawn by: D. Wiley Anderson, Architect, Richmond, VA; Contractor: Owner; Commissioned by: Kingsland Land Corp.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 17426, Three Stores, Chamberlayne and Lombardy Sts., Address: 2532-2534-2536 Lombardy St., 1926 (Folder 1124)
      Drawn by: Sitterding, Carneal, Davis Co.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Charles G. Morris; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 17209, Service Building for the Jones Motor Car Co., Address: 3001-3005 Cutshaw Ave., 1926 (Folder 567)
      Drawn by: Henry T. Barnham; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Jones Motor Car Co.; Notes: Two story brick and glass automobile service building.
    - Store - Permit Number: 16110, Five Stores, Address: 3007, 3009, 3011, 1013, 1015 Westhampton St., 1926 (Folder 1572)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: J. W. Hall; Commissioned by: Walter C. Schaft; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 16739, Store Bldg. 214 - 16 E. Broad Street for Mrs. Rita B. Strauss, Address: 214 - 216 E. Broad St., 1926 (Folder 1271)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: F. W. Boatwright; Commissioned by: Bryan Bear Est. (?); Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 17467, Store for Shepherds, Inc., Address: 412 E. Grace St., 1926 (Folder 1123)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: P. C. Abbott; Notes: The drawings identify the address as 408 Grace but the building was actually constructed at 412.
    - Store - Permit Number: 17373, Stores for Chas. A. Phillips & Co., Address: 100-102-104 E. Grace St., 1926 (Folder 1121)
      Drawn by: Carl M. Linder, Architect, State and City Bank Bldg., Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Chas. M. Phillips; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 14633A, Alterations and Additions to Store Building, Miller & Rhoads, Address: 521 W. Broad St., 1926 (Folder 1236)
      Drawn by: Bascom J. Rowlett, Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia, Associated Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: J. T. Wilson; Commissioned by: Miller & Rhoads; Notes: Alterations to Sixth and Broad streets portion of the building.
    - Store - Permit Number: 14975A, Alterations to W. T. Grant Building, Address: 321 E. Broad St., 1926 (Folder 1526)
      Drawn by: A. F. Evans, Architect, 455 7th Ave., New York City; Contractor: J. T. Wilson Construction; Commissioned by: P. H. Mayo Est.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 14767A, Alterations - Building No. 401 East Franklin St., Address: 401 E. Franklin St., 1926 (Folder 1269)
      Drawn by: L. P. Hartsook, Architect, American National Bank Bldg., Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: W. L. Ragland; Commissioned by: T. Garnett Tabb; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 18032, Store Building for Henry R. Haase, Address: 421 E. Franklin St., 1927 (Folder 1578)
      Drawn by: Carl M. Lindner, Architect, State and City Bank Bldg., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Henry R. Haase; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: N/A, Store Building for Mr. G. G. Worsham, Address: 505 E. Grace St., 1927 (Folder 1641)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: G. G. Worsham; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 18565, Store and Office Building, Address: 507 E. Franklin St., 1927 (Folder 1353)
      Drawn by: W. H. Pringle, Architect; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Muhleman & Kayhoe, Inc.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 17961, Store Building, Address: 2925 W. Marshall St., 1927 (Folder 1581)
      Drawn by: City Building Corp.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: R. K. Carter; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 18224, Store Building - A. L .Straus & Others, Address: 413 E. Broad St., 1927 (Folder 1624)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Schwarzschild - Nelson & Straus; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 18154, Store Building, Address: 6 - 10 E. Grace St., 1927 (Folder 1176)
      Drawn by: Carl M. Lindner, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: W. J. Anderson; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 18225, New Studio Building for Mr. W. W. Foster, Address: 404 E. Grace St., 1927 (Folder 1631)
      Drawn by: Henry T. Barnham, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: W. W. Foster; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 15502A, Alterations in Building, 1010 & 1012 W. Cary St., for H. Seldon Taylor & Son., Address: 1010, 1012 W. Cary St., 1927 (Folder 1687)
      Drawn by: Lee & Jardine, Engineers, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Thomas L. Moore; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 17803, 17804, Three Family Flat & Stores, Carolina Ave. & Milton Sts., Highland Park, Address: 913, 915, 917, 919 Milton St. and 3320 Carolina Ave., 1927 (Folder 1350)
      Drawn by: Bascom J. Rowlett, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: S. L. Manson; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 18223, Store Building for the Union Securities & Reality Corp., Address: 1511 Hull St., 1927 (Folder 1633)
      Drawn by: Marcellus E. Wright, Architect; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Union Securities Corp.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 18183, Additions and Alterations, Mrs. L. Sauer Dunston, West Broad Street, City., Address: 2020 W. Broad St., 1927 (Folder 1635)
      Drawn by: Matt P. Will; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: S. S. Dunston; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 18186, Three Stores & Office Building on Sites 203 & 205 Franklin Street, Address: 203, 205, 207 E. Franklin St., 1927 (Folder 1636)
      Drawn by: William C. West, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: C. E. Vonderslice & J. R. Williams; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 17613, Seven Stores on Bellevue Avenue, Address: 1201, 1203, 1205, 1207, 1209, 1211, 1213 Bellevue Ave., 1927 (Folder 1617)
      Drawn by: City Building Corporation; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: H. T. Eubank; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 19336, Cadillac & La Salle Bld'g., S. E. Cor. Broad & West Sts. for The Jones Motor Car Co., Address: 2923 W. Broad St., 1928 (Folder 1649)
      Drawn by: Henry T. Barnham. Architect & Engineer, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: E. L. Bass and Bro.; Commissioned by: Jones Motor Car Co.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 19735, Store Building, Address: 11 E. Grace St., 1928 (Folder 1714)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: John E. Fahed; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 18928, 16424A, Store & Office Building, The Corley Co., Inc., Address: 213 -214 E. Broad St., 1928 (Folder 1605)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Jones and Conquest; Commissioned by: Jas. W. Allison, The Corley Co.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 19284, Four Shops, Address: 210 E. Franklin St., 1928 (Folder 1646)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Sallie R. McAdams; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 19734, Building for Mr. Herold Hoffheimer, 2808 W. Broad St., Address: 2816 - 2818 W. Broad St., 1928 (Folder 1721)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Herold Hoffheimer; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 18994, Store Building, Address: 308 E. Grace St., 1928 (Folder 1592)
      Drawn by: Carl M. Lindner, Architect, State & City Bank Bldg., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: W. H. Jenks; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 16583A, Alterations & Additions, Miller & Rhoads Inc., Address: 517 E. Broad St., 1928 (Folder 1652)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Alvin Hutzler; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 19462, Stores for W. J. Anderson, Address: 424 E. Grace St., 1928 (Folder 1741)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Clairborne and Taylor; Commissioned by: William J. Anderson; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 20677, Store and Office Building for Wise Granite and Construction Co., Address: 719 E. Grace St., 1929 (Folder 1864)
      Drawn by: Marcellus E. Wright, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: Wise Granite and Construction; Commissioned by: Wise Granite & Construction Co.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 20405, Store Building, Six and Franklin Streets, Maj. C. L. Massie, Owner, Address: 508, 510, 512 E. Franklin St., 1929 (Folder 1782)
      Drawn by: Bascom J. Rowlett, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: C. L. Massie; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 19831, Broad - Grace Arcade, Address: 204 - 212 N. 3rd. St., 215 - 217 E. Broad St., 216 - 226 E. Grace St., 1929 (Folder 1745)
      Drawn by: John Ederson, New York City - Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Richmond, Virginia, Associated Architects; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Broad Grace Arcade Corp.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 20072, Store Building for Wise Granite and Construction Co., Address: 2701 W. Broad St., 1929 (Folder 1855)
      Drawn by: Marcellus E. Wright, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Wise Granite and Construction Co.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 20217, Store Bldgs., W. Broad St., for E. L. Frost, Esq., Address: 2720 W. Broad St., 1929 (Folder 1845)
      Drawn by: Henry T. Barnham, Arch't & Eng'r, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: E. L. Frost; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 20146, Store for Southern Asbestos Mfg. Co., Address: 306 E. Main St., 1929 (Folder 1842)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Southern Asbestos Manufacturing Co. Inc.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 20942, Two Story Store Building, Address: 304 E. Grace St., 1930 (Folder 1773)
      Drawn by: W. H. Pringle, Arc't, Muhleman & Kayhoe, Inc., Builders, 505 E. Franklin St.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: P. C. Abbott; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 21398, Business Building for W. J. Coulter, Address: 3817 W. Broad St., 1930 (Folder 1834)
    - Store - Permit Number: 18619A, Remodeling - Mercantile Building, Address: 500 E. Broad St., 1930 (Folder 1768)
      Drawn by: Budina & Helmpel, Architect & Engineer, Central National Bank Building, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Mrs. A. Virginia Mc George, et al; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 21085, Two Story Store, Address: 2420 E. Broad St., 1930 (Folder 1774)
      Drawn by: Carl M. Lindner, Architect, State & City Bank Bldg., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Virgil R. May; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 21017, Store and Office Building, 4th and Grace Sts., Address: 318, 320, 322 E. Grace St., 1930 (Folder 1756)
      Drawn by: W. H. Pringle; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Hillcrest Inc.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 21104, Store Building for O. D. Brinser, Address: 208 E. Grace St., 1930 (Folder 1815)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: O. D. Brinser; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 22421, Alterations and Additions to Undertaking Establishment, Address: 2502 East Marshall St., 1932 (Folder 1885)
      Drawn by: Carl M. Lindner, Architect, State & City Bank Bldg., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Charles J. Billups; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 22583, Business Building, No. 1 & 3 East Cary St., Address: 1 E. Cary St., 1933 (Folder 1880)
      Drawn by: Edward F. Sinnott, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: State & City Building Corp.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 20407A, Alterations to Store - Miller & Rhoads, Inc. [Broad St. and 6th Street facades], Address: 517 - 529 E. Broad St., 1933 (Folder 1919)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Doyle and Russell; Commissioned by: Miller & Rhoades and Hutzler - Boshen Estates; Notes: CD # 156, 156A.
    - Store - Permit Number: 20429A, Store No. 1068, F. W. Woolworth & Co., Atlanta, Ga., Address: 1317 Hull St., 1933 (Folder 1908)
      Drawn by: S. W. Storer, Consulting Engineer, Atlanta, Georgia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Associated Realty Corp.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 21128A, Alterations and Additions, Richmond Dry Goods Co., Inc., 7th & Cary Sts., Address: 11 South 7th St., 1934 (Folder 1944)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Richmond Dry Goods, Inc.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 21259A, Alterations and Additions to Friedman - Harry Marks Clothing Co., Inc., Address: 1400 - 1408 W. Marshall St., 1934 (Folder 1949)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: L. J. Trownstein; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 20888A, Alterations and Additions to Thalhimer Building [heating and cooling systems], Address: 605 - 627 E. Broad St., 1934 (Folder 1935)
      Drawn by: Harry Cooling & Equipment Company, Philadelphia, Pa.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Thalhimer Bros. Inc.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 23384, Southeastern Optical Company, Address: 212 E. Franklin St., 1935 (Folder 1939)
      Drawn by: Lee, Ballou & Van Dervoort; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Southeastern Optical Co., Inc.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 21868A, Air Conditioning Equipment for Miller & Rhoads, Address: 517 - 529 E. Broad St., 1935 (Folder 1952)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Engineers, Richmond, Va., York Ice Machinery Corporation, Philadelphia, PA.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Miller & Rhoads, Inc.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 22020A, Alterations and Additions - Richmond, Va. Store, Address: 19 E. Broad St., 1935 (Folder 1938)
      Drawn by: Lerner Stores Corporation, 354 Fourth Ave., New York, N.Y. Construction Department; Contractor: Lerner Stores Corp.; Commissioned by: Mrs. G. M. Schwarzschild; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 22160A, Fifth and Sixth Floor Additions, Thalhimer Bros., Address: 607, 609, 611, 1613 E. Broad St., 1935 (Folder 1931)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: John T. Wilson Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Bolling Lee / Thalhimer Bros.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 22539A, Electric Stairway layout for Miller and Rhoads, Address: 517-19 E. Broad St., 1936 (Folder 2593)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects and Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Westinghouse Electrical Elevator, Co., Chicago; Commissioned by: Miller & Rhoads, Inc.; Notes: plans for installing an escalator. CD # 167.
    - Store - Permit Number: 23667, Store Building, #3020 - 3022 W. Cary St., for Mr. P. C. Abbott, Address: 3018 - 3022 W. Cary St., 1936 (Folder 1975)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: P. C. Abbott; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 22918A, Greentree's - Richmond, VA, Address: 701 - 703 E. Broad St., 1936 (Folder 1965)
      Drawn by: Designing Service, American Store Equipment Corp., New York, Detroit, Chicago; Contractor: Doyle and Russell; Commissioned by: Tree Realty Corp.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 23114A, Alterations and Additions to 1319 Hull St. For Standard Drug Co., Inc., Address: 1319 Hull St., 1936 (Folder 2073)
      Drawn by: J. Binford Walford, Architect, successor to Charles M. Robinson, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Standard Shares, Inc.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 22529A, Charles Stores Co., Inc., Address: 7-19 E. Broad St., 1936 (Folder 2592)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Charles Stores Construction; Commissioned by: Zipporah M. Cohen Est.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 22620A, Addition to Building, Richmond Dry Goods Co., Inc., Address: 11 South 7th St., 1936 (Folder 1977)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Pocahontas Building Corp.; Notes:
    - Store - Permit Number: 23586, Broad & 6th St. Addition, Thalhimer Brothers, Address: 601 E. Broad St., 1936 (Folder 1971)